{
    "question": "When your friend has a trouble,how hard it is will never...you fnom helping them",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<h3>jawabannya: stop</h3><p></p><p>when your friend has a trouble,how hard it is will never <strong><em><u>stop</u></em></strong> your from helping them</p><p></p><p><em>( ketika temanmu dalam kesulitan, betapa sulitnya itu tidak akan pernah menghentikanmu untuk membantu mereka</em><em>)</em></p><p></p><p><em>semoga</em><em> </em><em>membantu</em><em>.</em></p><p></p><p></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "whatt-should-we-do-before-and-after-doing-something-838",
            "question": "Whatt Should we do before and after doing something?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You can do anything Play, eat and study</p><p><strong></strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "m-ch-n-c-what-word-is-on-the-side-428",
            "question": "M_CH_N_C what word is on the side \u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>M_CH_N_C  kata apa yang ada disamping:</p><p>(MECHANIC)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>M_CH_N_C what word is on the side</p><p>Answer:Mechanic</p><p></p><p><strong><em><u>MAAF</u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong><strong><em><u>KALAU</u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong><strong><em><u>SALAH</u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong></p><p><strong><em>SEMOGA BERMANFAAT</em></strong><strong><em> </em></strong></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><h2><strong><em><u>JADI</u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong><strong><em><u>KAN YANG</u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong><strong><em><u>TERBAIK </u></em></strong><strong><em><u> </u></em></strong></h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-dialogue-below-is-for-questions-no-8-10-jasminewhat-did-you-494",
            "question": "The dialogue below is for questions no 8-10    Jasmine:what did you(8)....last night\r\nTere:i(9).....a concert' with my sister\r\nJasmine:how(10).....the concert'?\r\nTere:it was really interesting.it was the amazing concert' ever.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>8. do</p><p>9. watched</p><p>10. was</p><p></p><p>Semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah. Kalo bener jan lupa jadiin jawaban tercerdas yak\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1fill-in-the-blanks-with-the-correct-adjectives-aorchild-is-s-376",
            "question": "1.fill in the blanks with the correct adjectives.    a.orchild is s very .... in the world!!\r\nb.i'am a ....... student!!\r\n\r\n2. Fill in teh blanks with the correct be (is,am,or are)\r\na.jacklyn ... my best friend!!\r\nb.they ...at school now!!\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>2. a. Jackly Is My Best Friend</p><p>b.  They Are At School Now</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>No 1 gk gw jawab soalnya gak jelas dan lu pake pp KPopler/BTS :v</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "5-i-saw-an-accident-last-night-somebody-an-ambulance-bu-979",
            "question": "5. i saw an accident last night. somebody \u2026\u2026..an ambulance but nobody \u2026\u2026 so the ambulance \u2026\u2026\u2026..    a. called \u2013 was injured \u2013 wasn\u2019t needed\r\nb. called \u2013 injured \u2013 didn\u2019t need \r\nc. was called \u2013 was injured \u2013 wasn\u2019t needed \r\nd. called \u2013 injured \u2013 wasn\u2019t needed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A.Called-Was Injured-Wasn&#039;t Needed</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Semoga Membantu!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A) Called - Was Injured - Wasn&#039;t Needed</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>I saw an accident last night. Somebody <strong>called</strong><strong> </strong>an ambulance but nobody <strong>was</strong><strong> </strong><strong>injured</strong><strong> </strong>so the ambulance <strong>wasn&#039;t</strong><strong> </strong><strong>needed</strong><strong>.</strong> (Aku melihat sebuah kecelakaan tadi malam. Seseorang <strong>menelepon</strong> sebuah ambulans namun tidak ada <strong>yang</strong> <strong>terluka</strong> sehingga ambulans tersebut <strong>tidak diperlukan</strong>) </p><p></p><p>Karena dia di masa lalu, maka kita gunakan simple past Dan past perfect. </p><p></p><p>V1            V2           V3</p><p>Call       Called     Called</p><p></p><ul><li>Untuk kesatu, kita gunakan Called karena kalimat tersebut lebih sesuai dengan kata called. </li><li>Untuk kedua, kita gunakan Was Injured karena pada bagian tersebut lebih logis bila diartikan sebagai \"tidak ada yang terluka/nobody was injured\" dibandingkan \"tidak ada terluka/nobody injured\"</li><li>Untuk ketiga, kita gunakan Wasn&#039;t Needed karena artinya adalah tidak diperlukan sedangkan jawaban yang tidak tepat adalah didn&#039;t need karena artinya tidak perlu. </li></ul><p></p><p>Jadi jawaban yang tepat adalah </p><p>A) Called - Was Injured - Wasn&#039;t Needed</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-following-text-to-answer-the-q-pink-beach-last-holiday-238",
            "question": "Read the following text to answer the q.    Pink Beach\r\nLast holiday I went to Komodo island. There is a gorgeous beach which has pink colored-sand. The\r\nbeach is called Pink Beach or Pantai Merah Muda,\r\nIl's a huge beach with a calm wave. When I looked it closely, I could see that it actually an ordinary\r\nwhite beach sand. But there are a lot of crushed corals and minerals that make it looks pink. Pink beach is a\r\nspecial beach, There's no one beach in this world has a beautiful pink sand like this.\r\n1. What is the text about?\r\n2. Where is it located ?\r\n3. Why the sand has pink color?\r\n4. Why does the writer think that Pink Beach is a special one?\r\n5.\r\n\" ....... It actually an ordinary white beach sand.\"\r\nWhat is the Indonesian translation of the underlined word ?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>1. Pink beach </p><p>2. Komodo Island</p><p>3. Because a lot of crushed corals and minerals make the sand  looks pink</p><p>4. because  there&#039;s no one beach in this world has a beautiful pink sand like that</p><p>5. mana kata bergaris bawah nya?</p><p></p><p>semoga bermanfaat.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>1.pink beach </p><p>2.in comodo island</p><p>3.Because that is a gorgeous beach</p><p>4.Because that&#039;s beach verry langkah </p><p>5.pantai merah. </p><p></p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> SEMOGA TIDAK MEMBANTU </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-grade-is-cindy-in-667",
            "question": "What grade is cindy in?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>dek ada dikasi cerita ga?</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>pertanyaannya kurang jelas..</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "dinda-run-so-fast-because-there-be-a-dog-mia-and-her-friend-566",
            "question": "Dinda    (run) so fast because there\r\n(be) a dog\r\nMia and her friend\r\n(borrow) some books from the library\r\nThe school janitor\r\n(sweep) the floor last night.\r\nMr Betty\r\n(teach) and\r\n(speak) English in the class.\r\nMy family\r\n(miss) the plane because we (wake up) late\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Dinda is running so fast because there is a dog</p><p>Mia and her friends are borrowing some books from the library</p><p>The school janitor was sweeping the floor last night</p><p>My Betty teaches and speaks English in the class</p><p>My Family missed the plane because we woke up late</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "20-she-a-diligent-girl-21-they-to-the-li-266",
            "question": "20. She .......... a diligent girl    21. They ........... to the library by bus\r\n22. Shinta ............ milk every morning\r\n23. What can you see in the park?\r\n24. My mother likes cook\r\nCook in Indonesia is .....\r\n25. My father likes go to work\r\nWork in Indonesia is ...... tolong kak\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>20. is</p><p>21. are go</p><p>22. always drinks</p><p>23. in the park we can see flowers, chairs, and trees.</p><p>24. artinya memasak</p><p>25. artinya bekerja</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "change-these-sentences-into-simple-past-tense-a-all-the-student-394",
            "question": "Change these sentences into simple past tense.    a. All the\r\n\r\nstudents in this school clean all the part of their school to face the Independence day.\r\n\r\nb. Our\r\n\r\nheadmaster gives punishment to the students who don't wear uniform.\r\n\r\n\r\nBantu jawab kak. jgn ngasal ya kakk\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "All the students in this school cleaned all the part of their school to face the independence day<br><br>Our headmaster gave punishment to the students who did not wear uniform<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>a. All the students cleaned all the part of their school to faced the independence day. </p><p></p><p></p><p>b. Our headmaster gave punishment to the students who didn&#039;t wear uniform. </p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}